hello everyone this is E on ey censored
Supernatural Bible chains on YouTube and
today is Saturday the 17th of February
2024 thank you for praying for
me I've really needed
it I wanted to go ahead and tell you
that my latest book is now available on
Amazon and I've titled it pollution
corruption and nature and and this has
over
600 King James Bible verses and
inclusive of a few verses from other
Bible Bibles English Bibles but 600
Bible verses that have been
altered related to this topic of
pollution corruption and nature and I'm
going to show you some examples our
bibles are supernaturally changing
preparing the way for the Antichrist
we're finding nonsense versus doctrinal
errors emoticons new people word
switches words
erased grammatical errors punctuation
errors spelling errors nonsense versus
and on and on it goes it's really crazy
and it's time to wake up in Jesus name
let me show you what it says on
Amazon and as for example I want to tell
you what new words you'll see in this
Bible pollution corruption nature
Environ Apes corn ferrets peacocks
cloudy caca cronies pigar and much
more there's so many new words in the
Bible related to agriculture related to
farming that was never there
before and I believe that there is an
Alchemy that's going
on in changing scripture through black
magic our Bibles in our own homes are
changing supernaturally and it's totally
bizarre but absolutely happening and
it's time to wake up in Jesus name let
me read some of the verses that are now
in the Bible and I'm going to start
here here we go and I want to show you
this is just a list of some of the new
words this is on one of the pages the
very beginning of the book and I show
how words like apes peacocks corn test
nuts trees notice the spelling error
dainty Meats gleed garlic melons caco
cows cockatrice pollution pollute
Environ oil olive corruption nature
parch corn meal time Pig
AR pulse naughty figs
cloudy shambles shittum sycamor misspelt
science and asses those are just some of
the new words that are found in the King
James Bible related to
pollution and um nature and so forth now
let me go ahead and read some of these
new verses to you included in this book
there are four verses on each page so 1
Chronicles 12:40 says this today in the
King James Bible moreover they that were
nigh
them even unto issachar and zebulun and
navelli brought Bread on
asses and on camels and on mules and on
oxen and meat meal cakes of figs and
bunches of raisins and wine and oil and
oxen and sheep abundantly for there was
joy in
Israel Exodus 39:34 and the covering of
ram skins died red and the covering of
badger skins and the veil of the
covering Isaiah 56 two blessed is the
man that doeth this and the son of man
that layeth hold on it and keepeth the
Sabbath from polluting it and keepeth
his hand from doing any
evil Leviticus
22:21 and whosoever offereth a sacrifice
of Peace offerings unto the Lord to
accomplish his vow or a free will
offering in beaves or sheep it shall be
perfect to be accepted accepted there
shall be no blemish
[Music]
therein 1st Chronicles 20:3 and he
brought out the people that were in it
and cut them with saws and with Harrows
of iron and with
axes even so D dealt David with all the
cities of the children of Aman and David
and all the people returned to
Jerusalem Exodus 9:3 behold the hand of
the Lord is upon thy cattle which is in
the field upon the horses upon the asses
upon the camels upon the oxen and upon
the sheep and there shall be a very
Grievous
Marine Isaiah 566 also the sons of the
stranger that join themselves to the
Lord to serve him and to love the name
of the Lord to be his servants everyone
that keepeth the Sabbath from polluting
it and taketh hold of my Covenant
Leviticus
22:28 and whether it be cow or
you ye shall not kill it and her young
both in one
day I'll read a couple more to you like
Isaiah 575 inflaming yourselves with
Idols under every Green Tree slaying the
children in the valleys Under The Cliffs
of the
Rocks Leviticus 23:14 and ye shall
neither you shall eat neither bread nor
Parts corn nor green
ears until the selfsame day that ye have
brought an offering unto your God it
shall be a statue forever throughout
your Generations in all your
dwellings can you detect can you discern
the changes do you
recognize the new words in these verses
the new doctrine here's another one
first Chronicles 27:28 and over the
olive trees and the sycamore trees that
were in the low Plains were balanan the
gorite and over the sellers of oil was
joash Ezekiel 15:2 son of man what is
the vine tree more than any tree or than
a branch which is among the trees trees
of the
forest and the last one I'll read to you
Isaiah
595 they hatch cockatrice eggs and weave
the spider's web he that eateth of their
eggs dth and that which is crushed breth
out into a
Viper okay I'll read one more Leviticus
24:2 command the children of Israel that
they bring unto thee pure oil
olive beaten for the light to cause the
lamps to burn
continually do you recognize these
verses that I'm reading to you have you
ever heard them
before because these are new to me new
words new
people it's absolutely crazy what we now
read in the
Bible and yet woefully the
church Bible scholars Bible pastors
Bible
teachers are woefully silent on what we
are now reading in our Bibles we find
new animals and by the way the word
animals is now erased from the King
James Bible that's one word that's
erased along with demon and demons
discernment holy of holies and on and on
it goes with words erased from the Bible
like the word music m i or
Jubilee or messiah in the New Testament
erased in the King James Bible but this
book again has over actually it has
exactly 600 Bible verses related to
pollution corruption and nature it's
time to wake up in jesus' name I hope
these tools are use ful for you and your
research on this very
diabolical
crazy events that we're seeing
today it's time to wake up it's time to
share the truth of what's happening to
get the truth out anyone who has ears to
hear that our bibles are under satanic
Siege be strong and courageous brothers
and sisters do not fear or be dismayed
for the Lord your God is with you
wherever you go until next time